import "Catalog/catalog.css";

// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {
  //#region Table de 0
  "0+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "1"
  },
  "0+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "2"
  },
  "0+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "3"
  },
  "0+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "0+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "0+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "0+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "0+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "0+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "0+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  //#endregion Table de zéro

  //#region Table de 1
  "1+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "1"
  },
  "1+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "2"
  },
  "1+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "3"
  },
  "1+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "1+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "1+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "1+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "1+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "1+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "1+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "1+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 1

  //#region Table de 2
  "2+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "2"
  },
  "2+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "3"
  },

  "2+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "2+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "2+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "2+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "2+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "2+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "2+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "2+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "2+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 2

  //#region Table de 3
  "3+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "3"
  },
  "3+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "3+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "3+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "3+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "3+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "3+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "3+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "3+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "3+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "3+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 3

  //#region Table de 4
  "4+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "4+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "4+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "4+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "4+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "4+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "4+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "4+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "4+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "4+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "4+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 4

  //#region Table de 5
  "5+0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "5+1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "5+2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "5+3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "5+4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "5+5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "5+6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "5+7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "5+8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "5+9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "5+10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 + 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 5

};